ZAN PETER SILAEN

Web Enthusiast

Lumbanlobu, Kab. Toba, Sumatera Utara| 0823-6987-7389 | zanpeter05@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Currently a 6th semester student at Institut Teknologi Del, focusing on Web Development and have several experiences related to Problem Solving while studying at Institut Teknologi Del. Always interested to explore and understands something new especially Web Development.

EXPERIENCE

Code.Id Internship

Web Developer | July 2023 - Present

 Build websites needed by companies in the form of integrating Coda and Clockify websites to make work easier

International Collegiate Programming Contest

Competitive Programming | November 2020 - December 2020

Algorithmic programming contest for college students.
Teams of three, representing their university, work to solve
the most real-world problems, fostering collaboration,
creativity, innovation, and the ability to perform under
pressure

Back End Developer Virtual Internship

Web Developer | July 2022 - August 2022

 Virtual internship regarding web developer with Back End Developer role. Learn several programming languages such as Java OOP, SQL Database, Spring Boot, and PostgreSQL

Departemen Komunikasi dan Informasi Badan Eksekutif Mahasiswa

Head of Departement | July 2022 - Juny 2023

 One part of BEM whose job is to disseminate information through social media and direct media.

PROJECTS

Integration Clockify and Coda

Web Developer | July 2023 - Present

 Build websites needed by companies in the form of integrating Coda and Clockify websites to make work easier

Clinic Website Development

Front-End & Back-End | October 2022 - January 2023

 Carry out website development starting from the requirements for the product owner to designing and building the system on the website that is being built.

Rencana Kerja dan Anggaran

Analyst & Mobile Developer | January 2023 - Mei 2023

 Doing website development and display on android regarding work plans and budgets at the Del Technology Institute

SKILLS

- Java
- C++
- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Laravel
- PHP
- Python
- Team work
- Good Communication
- Leadership

EDUCATION

Institut Teknologi Del | 2020 - Present

Bachelor of Informatics